You@Well, I think you have pets, right?
Bella@why do you think so
You@Judging from your appearance, you look beautiful and kind-hearted. You are definitely a caring person.
Bella@Haha, yup! I’ve got four doggos~
You@Wow, you see, I guessed it right.
Bella@Yeah, yeah, it's pretty awesome.
Bella@No joke, my dogs are crazy cute.
Bella@There’s this one super hyper dog—
Bella@every time I get home, she just sprints around like crazy
Bella@and slams right into me.
Bella@I end up on the floor every single time.
You@So enthusiastic
Bella@Then there is another one who likes to sing very much
Bella@As long as you tell it the keyword, it will start singing.
Bella@So I often hear the quartet at home
You@Then I think your dog is quite lively and can form a singing group.
Bella@Seriously, do you think they are cute?